pdfone.com 2018-03-02

# Privacy Policy - PDFone.com

**PDFONE Privacy Policy**

PDFONE respects your right to privacy and we understand that, as a visitor to our website you prefer to control the way you share your personal information and preferences. PDFONE provides this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to inform you of our practices about the way your information is collected online and how that information is used.

**Collection of Personal information**

Throughout this Policy the term “personal information” means information relating to an identified or identifiable individual (i.e. a natural person), such as your name, phone number, company name, email address. “PDFONE” refers to PDFONE, including its affiliates (also referred to as “we”, “us”, or “our”). In order to give you superior customer service, PDFONE collects your personal information in several ways.

**By using this website and/or by submitting personal information to PDFONE, you agree to the processing of your personal information in the manner provided in this Policy. If you do not agree with this Policy, please do not use this website or provide PDFONE with your personal information.**

**How Your Personal Information is Used**

PDFONE uses your personal information for the purposes described in this Policy. Please note that one or more purposes may apply simultaneously.

  1. **Provision of products and services.** We may use your personal information to deliver services and information (such as technical support, events, and training) you have requested; to develop our products and/or services; and for internal research to ensure the site is relevant to your needs. We may also use your personal information to provide you with service more relevant to you; for example, to display customized content in our website. We may combine personal information collected in connection with your use of a particular PDFONE product and/or service with other personal information we may hold about you, except where such personal information was collected for a different purpose.
  2. **Communicating with you and marketing.** We may use your personal information to communicate with you; for example, to provide information relating to our products and/or services you are using, to notify about product updates or to contact you for customer satisfaction queries. We may use your personal information for marketing or research purposes, for example, to conduct market research and we may, in accordance with applicable law, communicate information to you regarding new products, services, and special offers available from PDFONE.

If you do not wish to receive information from PDFONE, please let us know by emailing us at: admin@pdfone.com. In some cases, especially if you wish us to delete or cease the processing of your personal information, this may also mean that we may not be able to continue to provide the services to you.

**When We Disclose Personal Information**

PDFONE will not sell, rent or lease or otherwise disclose your personal information to third parties without your permission, unless otherwise stated below.

  1. PDFONE may share your personal information with authorized third parties who process personal information for PDFONE for the purposes described in this Policy. Such parties are not permitted to use your personal information for other purposes, and we require them to act consistently with this Policy and to use appropriate security measures to protect your personal information.
  2. PDFONE may be obligated to disclose your personal information by law action, subpoena, or local law.

**How We Protect your Personal Information**

PDFONE is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. While there are always risks associated with providing personal information, whether by phone, via the internet or otherwise, and no technology is completely safe, PDFONE takes appropriate technical and organisational information security measures to help minimise such risks.

Such measures include, where appropriate, the use of firewalls, secure server facilities, encryption, implementing proper access rights management systems, and other technically and commercially reasonable measures to provide appropriate protection for your personal information against unauthorised access, use or disclosure. Where appropriate, we may also take backup copies and use other such means to prevent accidental damage or destruction to your personal information.

We urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal information when you are on the Internet: change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

**Collecting Other Personal Information**

When you browse our PDFONE website, you are able to do it anonymously. Generally, we don’t collect personal information when you browse – not even your email address. Your browser, however, does automatically tell us the type of the computer and operating system you are using.

Like many websites, the PDFONE website use “cookie” technology. When you first connect to our sites, the cookie identifies your browser with a unique, random number. The cookies we use do not reveal any personal information about you. Cookies help us to register the most popular topics and pages of the site, as well as the time our visitors spend there. We use cookies to study traffic patterns on our site to improve and perfect it.

**Changes to this Statement**

If there are updates to the terms of PDFONE’s Privacy Policy, we will post those changes and update the revision date in this document, so you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have. We recommend that you review this Policy from time to time to learn of any changes to this Policy. Your continued use of our site signifies your acceptance of our Privacy Policy.

**Contact Information**

PDFONE welcomes your comments regarding this privacy policy, please contact us at:

E-mail: admin _@pdfone.com_.

June 2016
